Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. William Woodville Rockhill papers (MS Am 2121): Guide.
William Woodville Rockhill papers,
- I. Correspondence and other papers
  - Johnson, Nelson Trusler. Typed L.s.(Nelson Trusler Johnson) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Shanghai, 1 Nov 1913., (1322); 1l.
    Enclosed: Chinese characters copied from a page of Pei Wen Yun Fu; [Shanghai, 1 Nov 1913] 1l.
  - Johnson, Nelson Trusler. Typed L.s.(Nelson Trusler Johnson) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Shanghai, 1 Nov 1913., (1323); [2]p.
  - Johnson, Nelson Trusler. Typed L.s.(Nelson Trusler Johnson) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Shanghai, 24 Jan 1914., (1324); 1l.
  - Johnson, Robert Underwood, 1853-1937. A.L.s.(R. U. Johnson) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; New York 28 Oct 1903., (1325); ([2]p.)
  - Johnson, Robert Underwood, 1853-1937. Typed L.s.(R. U. Johnson) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 31 Oct 1903., (1326); ([1]p.)
  - Johnson, Robert Underwood, 1853-1937. Typed L.s.(R. U. Johnson) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 29 Sep 1904., (1327); 1l.
  - Jones, B. J. Typed L.s.(B. J. Jones) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 5 Mar 1914., (1328); ([2]p.)
  - Jones, Frank Hatch, 1854- A.L.s.(Frank H. Jones) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 12 Feb 1896., (1329); ([1]p.)
  - Jordan, Sir John N. A.L.s.(J. N. Jordan) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.] 15 May 1907., (1330); ([3]p.)
  - Jordan, Sir John N. A.L.s.(J. N. Jordan) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 17 Nov 1909., (1331); ([4]p.)
  - Jusserand, Jean Jules, 1855-1932. A.L.s.(Jusserand) to [?]; Washington, 17 Oct [1914]., (1332); ([4]p.)
  - Karkaria, R. P. A.L.s.(R. P. Karkaria) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Bombay, 19 Jun [1896]., (1333); ([2]p.)
    Enclosure: Typed article from The Times of India, 6 Jun 1898. 2l. With autograph annotation s.(R. P. Karkaria) to W[illiam] W[oodville] Rockhill; Bombay, 19 Jun [ 1896].
  - Kasnokov, A. A.L.s.(A. Kasnokov) to [William Woodville Rockhill;] [n.p.] 1/14 Jun 1913., (1334); ([2]p.)
  - Kasnokov, A. A.L.s.(A. Kasnokov) to [?]; [n.p., n.d.], (1335); ([4]p.)
  - Kasperowski, L. A.L.s.(L. Kasperowski) to the "Members of the family of Madame Greppin"; Geneve, 7 Jun 1913., (1336); ([2]p.)
  - Kavier, Alphonse. A.L.s.(Alph. Kavier) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Peking, 14 Dec 1888., (1337); ([1]p.)
  - Keane, Augustus Henry, 1833-1912. A.L.s.(A. H. Keane) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; South Hampstead, 15 Aug 1903., (1338); ([2]p.)
  - Keen, William Williams, 1837-1932. Typed L.s.(W. W. Keen) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Philadelphia, 5 Mar 1907., (1339); 1l.
  - Keene, Francis Bowler, Typed L.s.(Francis B. Keene) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Geneva, 27 Dec 1909., (1340); [2]p.
  - Keene, Francis Bowler, Typed L.s.(Francis B. Keene) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Geneva, 11 Jun 1913., (1341); [2]p.
  - Keene, Francis Bowler, Typescript s.(Francis Keene) of an entry in the Miscellaneous Record Book of the American Consulate, Geneva. [n.d.], (1342); 3l.
  - Keene, Francis Bowler, Typed L.s.(Francis B. Keene) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Geneva, 23 Jul 1913., (1343); [2]p.
  - Keene, Francis Bowler, Typed L.s.(Francis B. Keene) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Geneva, 23 Feb 1914., (1344); 1l.
  - Keeley, J. Transcript certification s.(J. Keeley); Yokohama, 27 Oct 1909., (1345); ([1]p.)
  - Keet, Alfred Ernest. Typed L.s.(A. E. Keet) to William Woodville Rockhill; New York, 1 Feb 1897., (1346); ([1]p.)
  - Kell, L. A.L.s.(L. Kell) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Paris, 22 Oct 1882., (1347); ([4]p.)
  - Kell, L. A.L.s.(L. Kell) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Paris, 22 Feb 1898., (1348); ([4]p.)
  - Kell, L. A. Postcard s.(L. Kell) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Paris, 10 Feb 1883., (1349); [1]p.
  - Kell, L. A. Postcard s.(L. Kell) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Paris, 6 Dec 1898., (1350); [1]p.
  - Kell, L. A.L.s.(L. Kell) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Paris, 30 Mar 1899., (1351); ([2]p.)
  - Kellogg, Martin, 1828-1903. A.L.s.(Martin Kellogg) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Berkeley, 15 Dec 1890., (1352); 2l.
  - Kellogg, Samuel Henry, 1839-1899. A.L.s.(S. H. Kellogg) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Allegheny, 30 May [1881]., (1353); ([2]p.)
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J. Scott Keltie) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 15 Dec 1892., (1354); ([4]p.)
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J. Scott Keltie) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 22 Dec 1892., (1355); ([3]p.)
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J. S. Keltie) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 30 Dec [1892]., (1356); ([2]p.)
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J. S. Keltie) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 9 Jan [1893]., (1357); ([2]p.)
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J. S. Keltie) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 21 Jan [1893]., (1358); ([2]p.)
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J. S. Keltie) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 23 Jan [1893]., (1359); ([2]p.)
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J. Scott Keltie) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 26 Jan [1893]., (1360); ([6]p.)
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J. S. Keltie) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 14 Mar [1893]., (1361); ([2]p.)
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J. S. Keltie) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 24 May [1893]., (1362); ([2]p.)
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J. S. Keltie) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 24 Jun 1893., (1363); ([2]p.)
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J. S. Keltie) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 10 Aug [1893]., (1364); ([4]p.)
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J. S. Keltie) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 30 Aug 1893., (1365); ([2]p.)
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J. S. Keltie) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 29 Sep [1893]., (1366); ([3]p.)
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J. S. Keltie) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 1 Dec [1893]., (1367); [2]p.
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J. S. Keltie) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 17 Jan [1894]., (1368); [2]p.
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J. S. Keltie) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 7 Mar 1894., (1369); ([3]p.)
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J. S. Keltie) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 4 Oct 1894., (1370); [2]p.
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J. S. Keltie) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 19 Oct [1894]., (1371); 1l.
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J. S. Keltie) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 29 Dec 1894., (1372); ([2]p.)
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J. S. Keltie) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 28 Mar 1895., (1373); [2]p.
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J. S. Keltie) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 20 Apr [1895]., (1374); 1l.
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J. S. Keltie) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 5 Jun 1895., (1375); ([1]p.)
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. Typed L.s.(J. S. Keltie) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 3 Oct 1895., (1376); 1l.
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J.Keltie) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 5 Feb [1896]., (1376a); ([4]p.)
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J. S. Keltie) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 2 Mar [1896]., (1377); ([2]p.)
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. Ms.L.s.(J. S. Keltie) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; London, 3 Apr 1897., (1378); ([2]p.)
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J. S. Keltie) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; London, 24 Jun [1897]., (1379); ([3]p.)
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J.Keltie) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; London, 3 Dec [1897]., (1379a); (2l.)
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(H.S.Keltie) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; London, 8 Dec [1897]., (1379b); ([4]p.)
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J. S. Keltie) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; London, 4 Jan [1898]., (1380); ([2]p.)
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J. S. Keltie) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 15 Jul [1898]., (1381); ([3]p.)
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J. S. Keltie) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 5 Apr [1899]., (1382); ([3]p.)
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J. S. Keltie) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 13 Apr [1899]., (1383); ([2]p.)
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J. S. Keltie) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 27 Apr [1899]., (1384); ([2]p.)
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J. S. Keltie) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 14 Jun [1899]., (1385); ([4]p.)
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J. S. Keltie) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 27 Jun [1899]., (1386); ([2]p.)
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J. S. Keltie) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 3 Jul [1899]., (1387); ([3]p.)
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J. S. Keltie) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 7 Jul [1899]., (1388); ([2]p.)
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J. S. Keltie) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 29 Aug [1899]., (1389); ([4]p.)
  - Keltie, Sir John, Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J. S. Keltie) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 25 Sep [1899]., (1390); ([3]p.)
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J. S. Keltie) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; London, 4 Dec [1899]., (1391); ([2]p.)
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J. S. Keltie) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; London, 26 Jan 1900., (1392); ([2]p.)
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J. S. Keltie) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 1 Feb [1900]., (1393); ([2]p.)
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J. S. Keltie) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 26 Feb [1900]., (1394); ([2]p.)
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J. S. Keltie) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; London, 31 Mar [1903]., (1395); ([2]p.)
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J. S. Keltie) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; London, 29 May [1903]., (1396); ([3]p.)
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J. S. Keltie) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; London, 6 Jul [1903]., (1397); ([2]p.)
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. Typed L.s.(J. Scott Keltie) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 30 Jun 1904., (1398); 1l.
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. Typed L.s.(J.S. Keltie) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; London, 4 Nov 1908., (1399); [2]p.
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. A.L.s.(J. S. Keltie) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; London, 10 Feb 1909., (1400); [2]p.
  - Keltie, Sir John Scott, 1840-1927. Typed L.s.(J. S. Keltie) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; London, 11 Sep 1912., (1401); [2]p.
  - Kemper, Del. A.L.s. (Del Kemper) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Amoy, 23 Apr 1897., (1402); ([3]p.)
  - Kempermann, [ ? ] A.L.s.(Kempermann) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Seoul, 1 Apr 1887., (1402a); ([2]p.)
  - Kiar, A. N. Typed L.s.(A. N. Kiar) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Kristiania, 25 Sep 1909., (1403); 3l.
  - Kidston, George Jardine, 1873- A.L.s.(George Kidston) to [Edith Howell (Perkins)] Rockhill; Havre, 17 Jan [1915]., (1404); ([5]p.)
    Also: Autograph annotation s.(E. R.) 1l.
  - Klatt, Johannes. A.L.s.(Dr. J. Klatt) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Berlin, 4 Feb 1889., (1405); ([2]p.)
  - Knapp, C. A.L.s.(C.Knapp) to [William] Woodville Rockhill; Neuchatel, 12 Mar 1895., (1405a); (2l.)
  - Knapp, C. A.N.s.(C.Knapp) to [William] Woodville Rockhill; Neuchatel, 17 Jun 1895., (1405b); (1l.)
  - Kniazeff, Leonide, A.L.s.(Leonide Kniazeff) to [?]; [n.p., n.d.], (1406); ([1]p.)
    In French. Enclosed: Calling card with autograph annotation.
  - Knox, Philander Chase, 1853- Typed L.s.(P. C. Knox) to William [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 4 Aug 1909., (1407); 1l.
  - Knox, Philander Chase, 1853- Typescript Telegram s.(Knox) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; [Washington, n.d.], (1408); 1l.
  - Knox, Philander Chase, 1853- Typescript of Telegram s. (Knox) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; [Washington, 1909], (1409); 3l.
  - Knox, Philander Chase, 1853- Typescript of Telegram s.(Knox) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; [n.p. 1909] Also: Typescript of Telegram s.(Rockhill) to [Philander Chase [Knox] St. Petersburg, [1909] Also: Typescript of Telegram s.(Knox) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Washington [1909], (1410); 2l.
  - Knox, Philander Chase, 1853- Typescript of Telegram (Knox) to [ ? ]; London[?], 6 Nov 1909., (1410a); 1l.
  - Knox, Philander Chase, 1853- Typescripts of Telegrams (Knox, Blanchard., and Wilson.) to [ ? ]; St. Petersburg, 15 Dec 1909., (1410b); 1l.
  - Knox, Philander Chase, 1853- Typescript of Telegram s.(Knox) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; [Washington] 6 Jun [?], (1411); 2l.
  - Knox, Philander Chase, 1853- Typescript of Telegram s.(Knox) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; [Washington] 9 Jun [1911] Also: Typescript of Telegram s.(Rockhill) to [Philander Chase Knox]; St. Petersburg, 10 Jun [1911], (1412); 1l.
  - Knox, Philander Chase, 1853- Typed L.s.(P. C. Knox) to William [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 17 Jun 1911., (1412a); ([3]p.)
  - Knox, Philander, Chase, 1853- Typescript of Telegram s.(Knox) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Washington, 17 Jun [1911], (1413); 1l.
  - Knox, Philander Chase, 1853- Typescript (c.c.) to Telegram s.(Knox) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; [Washington] [29 Jun 1911], (1414); 1l.
  - Knox, Philander Chase, 1853- Typescript of cable s.(Knox) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 18 Jul [1911], (1415); 1l.
  - Knox, Philander Chase, 1853- Typed L.s.(P. King) to William [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 23 Nov 1911., (1416); 1l.
    Enllosure: Typescript s.(P. C. Knox) to Jacob Schiff; Washington, 23 Nov 1911. 1l.
  - Knox, Philander Chase, 1853- Typescript of Telegram s.(Knox) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; [Washington] 27 Dec [?] Also: Typescript of Telegram s.(Rockhill) to [Philander Chase Knox]; [St. Petersburg] 29 Dec [?], (1417); 1l.
  - Knox, Philander Chase, 1853- Typed L.s.(P. Knox) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Washington, 16 Nov 1912., (1418); 1l.
  - Knox, Philander Chase, 1853- Typescript of L.(P.C.Knox) to Curtis Guild; Washington, 26 Feb 1913., (1418a); 5l.
  - Koike, Chozo. Typed Copy of "Chino-Japanese Conventon relating to Railway connections at Antung"; 15 Nov 1911., (1419); 5l.
  - Kokovtsov, Vladimir Nikolaevich, 1853- A.L.s.(V. Kokovtsov) to Montgomery Schuyler; [n.p.] 12/25 Sep 1909., (1420); ([2]p.)
  - Kokovtsov, Vladimir Nikolaevich, 1853- Typescript of interview; St. Petersburg, 13 Dec 1909., (1421); 2l.
  - Kokovtsov, Vladimir Nikolaevich, 1853- A.L.s.(V. Kokovtsov) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; [n.p.] 17 Feb/2 Ma 1910., (1422); ([3]p.)
  - Kokovtsov, Vladimir Nikolaevich, 1853- A.L.s.(V. Kokovtsov) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; [n.p.] 22 Nov 1910., (1423); ([3]p.)
  - Kokovtsov, Vladimir Nikolaevich, 1853- Typed L.s.(V. Kokovtsov) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Rome, 15/28 Oct 1913., (1424); 2l.
  - Kolton, Georg. A.L.s.(Georg Kolton) to [William] Woodville Rockhill; Berlin, 1 Jul 1893., (1425); ([1]p.)
    In German. Includes: A.L.(?) to [?]; Washington, 23 Jul 1893. ([1]p.)
  - Kolton, Georg. Typed L.s.(Georg Kolton) to William Woodville Rockhill; Berlin, 10 Jun 1903., (1426); ([1]p.)
  - Komura, Jutaró, 1855-1911. A.L.s.(Jutaró Komura) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.] 26 Nov [?]., (1427); ([2]p.)
  - Kopschi, J. T. A.L.s.(J. T. Kopschi) 60 [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Shanghai, 30 Sep 1896., (1428); ([6]p.)
  - Krebs, M. C. A.L.s.(M. C. Krebs) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Balto, 3 May 1887., (1429); ([3]p.)
  - Krotkoff, Apollo v. Semeorich, 1848- Typescript of Agreement s.(Kortkoff); [n.p.] 1901., (1430); 3l.
  - Krotkoff, Apollo v. Semeorich, 1848- Typed L.s.(Krotkoff) to Sa, Acting Tartar General; Kuanghsu, 10/23 Jul 1901., (1431); 2l.
    Enclosed: Typescript of Agreement s.(Sa and Krotkoff); Kuanghsu, 10 Jul 1901. 3l.
  - Krishrhorpen, F. von A.L.s.(F. v. Krishrhorpen) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Berlin, 12 Oct 1891., (1432); ([3]p.)
  - Krishrhorpeh, F. von. A.L.s.(F. v. Krishrhorpen) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Berlin, 12 Oct 1891., (1433); ([3]p.)
  - Krishrhorpen, F. von. A.L.s.(F. v. Krishrhorpen) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Berlin, 4 Jul 1891., (1434); ([2]p.)
  - Kung, Hien-Ri Typed L.s.(T. C. Kung Hien-ri) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 12 Dec 1914., (1435); 1l.
    Enclosed: Newspapers clippings.
  - Lamsdorff, Vladimir Nikolaevich, graf, 1837-1907. Typescript of Note (unsigned); [n.p., n.d.], (1436); 1l.
  - Landelin, Ruth A.L.s.(Ruth Landelin) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Karlsbad 10 Sep 1910., (1436a); [4]p.
  - Lange, Mary S. A. Receipt s.(Mary S. Lange) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.] 5 Dec 1913., (1437); ([1]p.)
  - Lange, Mary S. A. Receipt s.(Mary S. Lange) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.] 4 Jun 1914., (1438); ([1]p.)
  - Lange, Mary S. A. Receipt s.(Mary S. Lange) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.] 4 Jun 1914., (1439); ([1]p.)
  - Langhorne, G. Typed L.s.(G. Langhorne) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Zamboanga, Mindanao, 28 Jul 1905., (1440); 3l.
  - Lane, William Coolidge, 1859-1931. Typed L.s.(Wm. C. Lane) to Kenneth Colegrove; Cambridge, 21 Nov 1921., (1441); 1l.
  - Langley, Samuel Pierpont, 1834-1906. Ms.L.s.(S. P. Langley) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, [n.d.], (1442); ([3]p.)
  - Langley, Samuel Pierpont, 1834-1906. Typed L.s.(S. P. Langley) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 19 Jun 1891., (1443); 2l.
    Enclosure: Typed L.s.(S. P. Langley) to W[illiam] W[oodville] Rockhill; Washington, 19 Jun 1891. 1l.
  - Langley, Samuel Pierpont, 1834-1906. Typed L.s.(S. P. Langley) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 9 Jan 1893., (1444); ([2]p.)
  - Langley, Samuel Pierpont, 1834-1906. Typed L.s.(S. P. Langley) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 24 Jan 1893., (1445); 1l.
  - Langley, Samuel Pierpont, 1834-1906. Typed L.s.(S. P. Langley) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 20 Dec 1894., (1446); ([2]p.)
  - Langley, Samuel Pierpont, 1834-1906. Typed L.s.(S. P. Langley) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 26 Mar 1895., (1447); ([1]p.)
  - Langley, Samuel Pierpont, 1834-1906. Typed L.s.(S. P. Langley) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 12 Jun 1897., (1448); ([1]p.)
  - Langley, Samuel Pierpont, 1834-1906. Typed L.s.(S. P. Langley) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 4 Feb 1898., (1449); 2l.
  - Langley, Samuel Pierpont, 1834-1906. Typed L.s.(S. P. Langley) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 17 Feb 1898., (1450); 2l.
  - Langley, Samuel Pierpont, 1834-1906. Typed L.s.(S. P. Langley) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 8 Nov 1901., (1451); 3l.
  - Langley Samuel Pierpont, 1834-1906. Typed L.s.(S. P. Dangley) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 21 Nov 1901., (1452); 1l.
  - Lanman, Charles Rockwell, 1850-1941. A.L.s.(C. R. Lanman) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Cambridge, 28 Oct 1887., (1453); 1l.
  - Lanman, Charles Rockwell, 1850-1941. A.L.s.(C. R. Lanman) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Darjeeling, 16 Mar 1889., (1454); ([1]p.)
  - Lanman, Charles Rockwell, 1850-1941. Typed L.s.(Charles R. Lanman) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Cambridge, 11 Jul 1896., (1455); 2l.
  - Lanman, Charles Rockwell. 1850-1941. Typed L.s.(Charles R. Lanman) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Cambridge, 16 Jul 1896., (1456); 2l.
  - Lanman, Charles Rockwell, 1850-1941. A.L.s.(C. R. Lanman) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; South West Harbor, 17 Aug 1896., (1457); 2l.
  - Lanman, Charles Rockwell, 1850-1941. Typed L.s.(C. R. Lanman) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Cambridge, 10 Apr 1900., (1458); 2l.
  - Danman, Charles Rockwell, 1850-1941. A.L.s.(C. R. Lanman) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Cambridge, 20 Apr 1902., (1459); 2l.
  - Lanman, Charles Rockwell, 1850-1941. Typed L.s.(C. R. Lanman) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Cambridge, 24 Apr 1900., (1460); 1l.
  - Lanman, Charles Rockwell, 1850-1941. Typed L.s.(Charles R. Lanman) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Cambridge, 28 Mar 1903., (1461); 1l.
  - Lanman, Charles Rockwell, 1850-1941. A.L.s.(C. R. Lanman) to [William Woodhill] Rockhill; Cambridge, 8 Dec 1903., (1462); ([2]p.)
  - Lanman, Charles Rockwell, 1850-1941. A.L.s.(C. R. Lanman) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Cambridge, 29 Nov 1905., (1463); 1l.
  - Lanman, Charles Rockwell, 1850-1941. Typed L.s.(Charles Lanman) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Cambridge, 4 Feb 1908., (1464); 1l.
  - Lansdell, Henry, 1841-1919. A.L.s.(Henry Lansdell) to [William] Woodville Rockhill; Blackheath, 22 Feb 1893., (1465); ([4]p.)
  - Lansdowne, Henry Charles Keith Petty-Fitzmaurice, 5th marquess of, 1845-1927. Typescript of L.s.(Lansdowne) to M. Cambon; [n.p.] 7 Mar 1902., (1466); 3l.
    Enclsoure: Typescript Note to M. Cambon; [n.p.] 2Apr 1902. 1l. Also: Typescript Memorandum; [n.p.] 3 /Apr 1902. 1l.
  - Lansing, Robert, 1864-1928. Ms.L.s.(Robert Lansing) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 2 Mar 1895., (1467); 1l.
  - Lansing, Robert, 1864-1928. Ms.L.s.(Robert Lansing) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Henderson Harbor, 19 Jul 1914., (1468); ([1]p.)
  - Lansing, Robert, 1864-1928. Typescript of L.s.(Robert Lansing) to "The American Group"; Washington, 13 Nov 1914., (1469); 1l.
    Enclosure: 2 Typescripts of Paraphrases of Telegram; [n.p.] 13 Nov 1914. 1l.
  - Larkin, Dorothy (Rockhill) Hoppin. A.L.s.(Dorothy) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.] 5 Jun [1913], (1470); ([15]p.)
  - Larkin, Dorothy, (Rockhill) Hoppin. Typed Telegram s.(Dorothy) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Bordighera, [Jun 1913], (1471); 1l.
  - Larkin, Dorothy (Rockhill) Hoppin. Typescript (c.c.) to Telegram s.(Dorothy) to [William] Woodville Rockhill 5 Jun [1913], (1472); 1l.
  - Larkin, Dorothy (Rockhill) Hoppin. 2 typed telegrams s.(Dorothy) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; 6 Jun [1913], (1473); 1l.
  - Larkin, Dorothy (Rockhill) Hoppin. Typed Telegram s.(Dorothy) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; 8 Jun [1913], (1474); 1l.
  - Larkin, Dorothy (Rockhill) Hoppin. A.L.s.(Hoppin) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Bordighera, 9 Jun [1913], (1475); ([11]p.)
  - Larkin, Dorothy (Rockhill) Hoppin. A.L.s.(Dorothy) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Paris, 16 May [1914], (1476); ([12]p.)
  - Larkin, Dorothy (Rockhill) Hoppin. A.L.s.(Dorothy) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Wien, 28 May [1914], (1477); ([4]p.)
  - Larkin, Dorothy (Rockhill) Hoppin. A.L.s.(Dorothy) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Paris, 29 Oct [1914], (1478); ([4]p.)
  - Lassupeni, Terrien de. A.L.s.(Terrien de Lassupeni) to [William] Woodville Rockhill; London, 23 May [1882]., (1479); ([1]p.)
  - Lassupeni, Terrien de. A.L.s.(Terrien de Lassupeni) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; London, 3 Jul [1882]., (1479a); ([2]p.)
  - Lassupeni, Terrien de. A.L.s.(Terrien de Lassupeni) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; London, 18 May [1893]., (1479b); ([3]p.)
  - Lassupeni, Terrien de. A.L.s.(Terrien de Lassupeni) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; London, 25 May [1883]., (1479c); ([4]p.)
  - Lassupeni, Terrien de. A.L.s.(Terrien de Lassupeni) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; London, 2 Jul [1883]., (1479d); ([2]p.)
  - Lassupeni, Terrien de. A.N.s.(Terrien de Lassupeni) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; London, 17 Sep [1883]., (1479e); (1l.)
  - Lassupeni, Terrien de. A.L.s.(Terrien de Lassupeni) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; London, 19 Sep [1883]., (1479f); [2]p.